Contact

lyfestyle.fitness_coach@yah oo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ruby-williams-a6943150 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Emergency Medicine Leadership Military

Ruby Williams

Clinical Nurse Manager of StARN Program Women's Services at HealthTrust:HCA

Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Summary

Experienced Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the Hospital & Health Care industry. Skilled in Nursing Management, Nonprofit Organizations, Internal Audit, HR Consulting, and Nursing Education. Strong healthcare services professional with a Master of Arts (MA) focused in Human Relations w/ Emphasis in Counseling from University of Oklahoma.

Experience

HealthTrust Workforce Solutions 3 years

StaRN Women's Services Clin.Edu.,MGR, May 2018 - Present (2 years 2 months)

Clinical Nurse Education 2017 - Present (3 years) RN Clinical Educator

Rodan & Fields Independent Consultant Executive Consultant May 2018 - Present (2 years 2 months)

Concentric Healthcare Staffing
Travel Registered Nurse
September 2017 - Present (2 years 10 months)
Nationwide

ICU, ER, L&D, Postpartum, Telemetry

Parallon East Florida Supply Chain Clinical Resource Director September 2016 - Present (3 years 10 months) WRMC, Plantation, Florida Clinically manage & coordinates the logistics for the Supply Management
Analysis Team (SMAT) Committee. Review all Supply Expense Cost Savings
& cost drivers with CFO and SMAT committee.

Navy Nurse

EMPOWERING GROWTH Founder & CEO January 2015 - Present (5 years 6 months)

Education

University of Oklahoma

Master of Arts (MA), Human Relations w/ Emphasis in

Counseling · (2003 - 2005)

Walden University

Doctor of Philosophy (PhD) current student, Higher Education/Higher

Education Administration · (2015)